[
    {
        "prompt": "Canoe.",
        "response": "Canoe help me with my homework?"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Merry.",
        "response": "Merry Christmas!"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Orange.",
        "response": "Orange you going to let me in?"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Anee.",
        "response": "Anee one you like!"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Iva.",
        "response": "I've a sore hand from knocking!"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dozen.",
        "response": "Dozen anybody want to let me in?"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Needle.",
        "response": "Needle little money for the movies."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Henrietta.",
        "response": "Henrietta worm that was in his apple."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Avenue.",
        "response": "Avenue knocked on this door before?"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Harry.",
        "response": "Harry up, it's cold out here!"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "A herd.",
        "response": "A herd you were home, so I came over!"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Adore.",
        "response": "Adore is between us. Open up!"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Otto.",
        "response": "Otto know. I've got amnesia."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "King Tut.",
        "response": "King Tut-key fried chicken!"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lettuce.",
        "response": "Lettuce in it's cold out here."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Noah.",
        "response": "Noah good place we can get something to eat?"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Robin.",
        "response": "Robin the piggy bank again."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dwayne.",
        "response": "Dwayne the bathtub, It's overflowing!"
    }
]
